<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>data&#43;science</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on data&#43;science</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to the Tidyverse</title>
      <link>/posts/tidyverse-covid-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/tidyverse-covid-19/</guid>
      <description>The tidyverse is a set of actively developed and well-maintained R packages to facilitate the typical data analysis workflow. Most but not all of the core tidyverse packages (there are now 8) were designed by Hadley Wickham, chief scientist at R Studio since 2013. He&amp;rsquo;s written a book, &lt;em&gt;R for Data Science&lt;/em&gt;, which is an incredible resource for all programming levels, and given several talks which are of course available on YouTube if you find yourself becoming curious too&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>img { border-radius: 50%; width: 20em; }  I’m Morgan, a second year computational biology / bioinformatics PhD student at the Experimental and Clinical Research Center in Berlin, Germany.
In the next two years I hope to (1) benchmark and advance the statistical methods being widely deployed in microbiome and multi-omics research in order to (2) better illuminate robust and covariate-aware host-microbiome interactions through various clinical collaborations.
Here is where I hope to digest and document some of what I’m learning for my research along the way, especially but not limited to statistical analysis in R.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resources/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s where I&amp;rsquo;ll eventually link to all the tagged/categorized resources I&amp;rsquo;ve used.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>